http://www.allfabflowers.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy provides information on how Always Fabulous Flowers manages personal information collected; including personal information collected through this website.
Always Fabulous Flowers realises the importance of ensuring that personal information held by the company is treated confidentially and is committed to ensuring that all personal information is only collected, disclosed, used and stored in accordance with the National Privacy Principles set out under the federal Privacy Act 1988.
What is 'personal information'?
'Personal Information' is information or an opinion (including information or an opinion forming part of a database) whether true or not, and whether recorded in a material form or not, about an individual whose identity is apparent, or can reasonably be ascertained, from the information or opinion
Use and disclosure of personal information
Any personal information that we collect will only be used and disclosed for the purpose for which it has been provided to us.
Personal information may need to be disclosed to external service providers engaged by Always Fabulous Flowers in order for those service providers to fulfil their service obligations to the firm.  For example:
IT service providers who assist in managing Always Fabulous Flowers's servers and networks may need to access client data in order to maintain the servers and networks;
Where personal information is disclosed to an external party, Always Fabulous Flowers will take steps to ensure that the external party treats such information confidentially and in accordance with the federal Privacy Act 1988.
Email Communications
If you have registered through our website to receive email communications from us, we may use your contact details to send you newsletters, marketing emails or invitations to Always Fabulous Flowers seminars or events, which may be of interest to you. However, you may at any time opt out of receiving such materials by completing our Online Enquiry Form. Upon receiving such a request, Always Fabulous Flowers will remove your contact details from our distribution lists.
Accessing and Correcting Personal Information
You may request us to provide you with access to personal information we hold about you. We will process all requests for access to personal information in accordance with the National Privacy Principles.  In most cases, we will provide you with access to your personal information. However, we may refuse access in certain situations as listed in the National Privacy Principles. If we refuse to give you access, we will provide you with reasons for our refusal.
If any personal information we hold about you is not accurate, complete or up to date,  please let us know and in most cases, we will use all reasonable efforts to update the information..
Personal information security
Always Fabulous Flowers is committed to keeping secure the data you provide to us and we will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration.
Changes to our privacy policy
From time to time it may be necessary for us to revise our privacy policy. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time without prior notice.  We will notify you of the changes by posting an updated version of the policy on our website.
Home
Weddings
Corporate
About Us
In The Media
Real Stories
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
© 1997 - 2020 Always Fabulous Flowers.
Web design by Pivotal Agency;
